Nick's Resume

Basic Information

Name: Nick Han
Phone Number: 718-715-6886

Email: <u>nickhan0228@gmail.com</u>

Professional Profile

I am a self-motivated, innovative, independent guy who has the ability to innovate and operate independently; I am also a great team player who possesses good communication skill and strong sense of responsibility; I have strong ambitions to challenge myself to get used to new fields which I never experienced.

Technical Skills

	Lotus Notes	3 years
\triangleright	Java, JSP, Struts, Spring, Hibernate	7 years
\triangleright	Weblogic, Websphere, Apache	6 years
\triangleright	Database (DB2, mysql)	7 years
>	Html5+CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery	5 years
\triangleright	PHP	2 years
>	Magento,WordPress	2 years

Certification

> IBM DB2 730, 731

Work Experience

Mozzign Inc
Sep. 2013 to April.2014

Java Developer New York, NY

Philips (China) Investment Co., Ltd. May. 2012 to April.2013

PMO/Project Manager Shanghai, China

> SB Design Inc March. 2011 to Feb.2012

Web Programmer New York, NY

> IBM Dalian GDC April 2007 to September 2010

I/T Specialist China

Project Experience

Project Name: LG Smart TV App, Jadeandjasper jewelry Website, Nuvico

Company: Mozzign Inc

Project Duration: Sep. 2013 to April. 2014

Project Description: Mozzign is a highly skilled professionals and multi-faceted

agency providing innovative solutions company. In this company, I did three projects. The first project was for providing solutions and maintainance for nuvico website. The second was designing and maintainance for magento project

second was designing and maintainance for magento project which was called Jadeandjasper jewelry website. The third project was the most significant and impressive project, which project was called LG Smart TV App about support section from LG CNS inc. In this project, as a core web developer, I was responsible for requirements analysis, design database, programming and testing. Via these projects, I really Improved my technique skills and understand how to deal with projects

risk problems by myself.

Skills Description: Java, JSP, MYSQLMagento, PHP, Html5+CSS3, JQuery

WebService, Spring MVC.

Project Name: Philips China official website

Company: Philips (China) Investment Co., Ltd.

Project Duration: May. 2012 to April.2013

Project Description: This project is purpose to create new products functions based

on the current Philips China website. There are many Philips own products, so in this case, we're creating promo center, e-shop center, SMS center, and Mobile center in order to provide a platform for Philips products. They are all separated project. In these projects, I was responsible for being enable every project to go smoothly from biz planning to go-live. So in this case, I need to coordinate between project team and

biz customer. Via these projects, I really improved my communicate skills with biz customer and understand how to control project risk and make good relationship with team

members as project manager.

Project Name: SB DesignCompany: SB Design Inc

Project Duration: March. 2011 to Feb. 2012

Project Description: SB Design is a PR Marketing project. In this project I was

responsible for database design, programming and testing.

Throughout this project, I really improved my project management skill, touch most popular skills, and

communicate skills

Skills Description: Java, Lotus Notes, Web service, Html5+CSS3,

JQuery, JavaScript, WordPress, MySQL

Project Name: IBM Global Delivery HR Application(GDHA)

Company: IBM China Company
Project Duration: Jan. 2010 to Sept. 2010

Project description: GDHA is an internal project for IBM Asian employees. I was

mainly responsible for maintain the project which is called 'PBC'. In this project, team member were located in different countries, and we worked together although some people I never met throughout the whole project. My communication

skill was improved through this project.

Skills description: Lotus Script, JavaScript, Java, and Domino Designer, DB2

Project Name: IGA Korea Development of Lotus Notes DB

Company: IBM China Company
Project Duration: Jan.2009 to Dec.2009

Project description: It's an IBM internal project which is used by huge banks,

financial companies and IBM internal employees. In this project, I was responsible for Lotus Noes DB development, such as IBM information management, IBM vacation System and so

on.

Skills description: : Lotus Script, JavaScript, Java, and Domino Designer, DB2

Project Name: Korea Telecom Freetel (KTF)

Company: IBM China Company

Project Duration: Auguest 2008 to Dec. 2008

Project description: KTF is a huge telecom company in Korea. There were more

than 1,000 people involved in this project. I was responsible for back end development. Parse the parameter which is from UI through web service, then program based on customer's requirement. Through this project, I gained a lot of team work

experience.

Skills description: Java, JavaScript, Web service, Oracle database

Project Name: Web Tools

Company: IBM China Company
Project Duration: January 2008 to July 2008

Project description: Web Tools is an internal project for IBM GERS support team in

order to measure employee's workload. In this project,I was responsible for backend java developer. Despite this project

was small, I experienced all the life cycle of system

development.

Skills description: Java, JSP, Ajax, JavaScript, Struts, Spring, Hibernate, DB2

Project Name: Eastern Insurance

Company: IBM China Company

Project Duration: July 2007 to January 2008

Project description: Eastern Insurance is an insurance company in Korea. In this

project, I was responsible for front end development. Use html, javascript and Ajax to develop UI based on the customer's

requirement.

Skills description: Javascript, NCRM, Ajax

Project Name: People Resource Management System(PRMS)

Company: IBM China Dalian GDC Project Duration: April 2007 to June 2007

Project description: PRMS is an IBM internal project for Korea team in order to

manage employee's attendance time. In this project, I was responsible for developing and testing for system. I improved my web development skills and obtained project experience

via this project.

Skills description: Java, JSP, JS, DB2

Education

Dalian Nationalities University, 2007 (China)
Bachelor Degree

Languages

- > Fluent in English
- Native in Korea
- Native in Chinese